RICHARD ALMEIDA

JUNIOR DATA ANALYST



✓ RichardAlmeida@hotmail.com

Mollywood, FL.

English & Spanish

SKILLS

- Excel . PowerPoint . Word
- SQL
- Tableau
- R & Python (novice)
- Data Visualization
- Analytical Skill (Facebook Ad Metrics)
- HTML CSS JAVA
- · Adobe Suite Tools
- Computer Literacy
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS
PROFFESIONAL CERTIFICATE
2022

KEISER UNIVERSITY 2007-2009

BROWARD COLLEGE 2004 - 2007

PROFILE

Highly motivated, team-oriented, and committed individual with several years of IT & web content creation. looking for a full-time position in Data Analytics in which I can grow my Analytical and Data visualization skills to work. serve, produce quality work, and excel.

EXPERIENCE

WEB CONTENT MANAGER

Shopify . Digital marketer . Sales

2016 - Present

- Complete projects from conception to development including logo design, web design, branding, & social media management.
- Integrate integral SEO technique & Meta keywords
- Utilize multiple software applications including; Photoshop,
 Illustrator, and Davinci resolve media editor.
- Managed Facebook Ads marketing strategies & analyzing Facebook Ads sales data metrics.

LAWERS OFFICE OF STEPHAN PLANT

Office Specialist . Head of IT

2010 - 2014

- Provide Office technical support for Desktops PC, Printers, Networking, Servers, & Software updates/drivers
- Website design including logo design, web design, branding, & social media management.
- Integrate integral SEO technique & Meta keywords
- Utilize multiple software applications including; Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, & Dreamweaver.